artoftime.com 2019-02-13

# Privacy Policy - Art of Time

Art Of Time is committed to protecting the privacy of all customers.

**Personal Information :**

Art Of Time may collect personally identifiable information such as name, postal address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card number, checking account number; This personal information is collected and used by ART OF TIME staff for the sole purpose of facilitating a business transaction.

**E-mail :**

Art Of Time does not sell or rent e-mail addresses to other organizations. Artoftime.com may generate e-mail for the following types of communication:

1\. Transactional e-mail, which is the result of a business transaction initiated with artoftime.com.

2\. Relationship e-mail, which is sent as an informational service because of a relationship with artoftime.com.

3\. Correspondence from ART OF TIME staff as a result of a communication initiated by customer.

**Mailing Lists :**

Art Of Time may occasionally send informational or promotional materials to customers. You may choose to exclude yourself from ART OF TIME mailings by contacting the Customer Services Department (see ART OF TIME contact Information), Postal mailing list's, comprised of full name and postal address, Will Not be sold to other organizations.

Third-party Agents :

Art Of Time uses third-party agents for several business purposes, including credit card validation, and shipping. These agents are permitted to use your personal information only to provide Art Of Time with a specific service and not for any other purpose. Art Of Time makes every effort to preserve your privacy, but we may need to disclose personal information when required by law.

 **If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you shouldcontact us immediately**
